[{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980246826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":18201,"timeElapsed":73084},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980251309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4480,"timeElapsed":77567},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980258061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":6750,"timeElapsed":84319},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980266496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8433,"timeElapsed":92754},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980278308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":11810,"timeElapsed":104566},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980286206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":7896,"timeElapsed":112464},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980295062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":8854,"timeElapsed":121320},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980303771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":8706,"timeElapsed":130029},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980310059,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":6285,"timeElapsed":136317},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":9896,"timeElapsed":148109},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980325463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3609,"timeElapsed":151721},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980328887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3422,"timeElapsed":155145},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980340139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":11250,"timeElapsed":166397},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980346607,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6465,"timeElapsed":172864},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980368600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":21992,"timeElapsed":194858},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5708,"timeElapsed":200569},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980378841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4529,"timeElapsed":205099},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980384884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6040,"timeElapsed":211141},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4950,"timeElapsed":216093},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980402578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":11480,"timeElapsed":228836},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980407809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":5229,"timeElapsed":234066},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3545,"timeElapsed":237613},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":15074,"timeElapsed":252689},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":7733,"timeElapsed":260423},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":5806,"timeElapsed":266232},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980451655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11680,"timeElapsed":277913},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980457129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":5472,"timeElapsed":283387},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3357,"timeElapsed":286746},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7253,"timeElapsed":295213},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980472338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3382,"timeElapsed":298596},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2259,"timeElapsed":300857},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980485017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":10415,"timeElapsed":311275},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980491280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6261,"timeElapsed":317537},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4561,"timeElapsed":322100},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4790,"timeElapsed":326892},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980505311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4675,"timeElapsed":331569},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980508727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3415,"timeElapsed":334985},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":8285,"timeElapsed":344516},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980521812,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3552,"timeElapsed":348070},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980524871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3057,"timeElapsed":351129},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980528507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3634,"timeElapsed":354765},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":8171,"timeElapsed":362937},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4943,"timeElapsed":367882},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3342,"timeElapsed":371226},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2634,"timeElapsed":373861},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980551922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":4317,"timeElapsed":378180},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980555558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3635,"timeElapsed":381816},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980564886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":8146,"timeElapsed":391144},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1893,"timeElapsed":393039},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2568,"timeElapsed":395609},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980576908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":7555,"timeElapsed":403166},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2772,"timeElapsed":405939},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3830,"timeElapsed":409771},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980587897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4382,"timeElapsed":414155},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980591720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3821,"timeElapsed":417978},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2878,"timeElapsed":420857},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980604765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":8700,"timeElapsed":431023},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2455,"timeElapsed":433479},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3691,"timeElapsed":437172},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2917,"timeElapsed":440092},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980620893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":7057,"timeElapsed":447151},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3666,"timeElapsed":450818},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980627391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2829,"timeElapsed":453649},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5269,"timeElapsed":458919},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4391,"timeElapsed":463312},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980643105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4805,"timeElapsed":469363},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980645309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2202,"timeElapsed":471567},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3162,"timeElapsed":474731},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":6505,"timeElapsed":481238},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2007,"timeElapsed":483248},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":5277,"timeElapsed":488526},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1650,"timeElapsed":490178},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666808,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2886,"timeElapsed":493066},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2195,"timeElapsed":495263},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980675098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5131,"timeElapsed":501356},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980677350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2250,"timeElapsed":503608},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980679539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2187,"timeElapsed":505797},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":22102,"timeElapsed":527900},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980703994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2350,"timeElapsed":530252},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980708485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4488,"timeElapsed":534742},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980710380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1893,"timeElapsed":536638},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2389,"timeElapsed":539028},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3423,"timeElapsed":542453},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":11599,"timeElapsed":555062},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980734873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6067,"timeElapsed":561131},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980737232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2357,"timeElapsed":563490},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980744909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7676,"timeElapsed":571167},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980750018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":5107,"timeElapsed":576276},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980755046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5026,"timeElapsed":581304},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980757031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1983,"timeElapsed":583289},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4592,"timeElapsed":587883},{"subjectID":"8m6166uo1u","prolificID":"673f6cafb1e5fb4499387cae","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23cf42b7454637b3afe","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2137,"timeElapsed":590022}]